https://dwklaw.com/dwkmars-privacy-policy/

Facebook
Twitter Free ConsultationFree ResourcesYour Case ValueBlogBurn & FireCar AccidentsDog Bite InjuriesEye InjuriesInsuranceMedical MalpracticeMotorcycle AccidentNegligent SecurityPediatric EyePersonal InjuryPremises LiabilityProduct LiabilityPublic SafetyTourist InjuriesTrucking AccidentsWater InjuriesAbout Our AttorneysVideo ChannelCharities We Work WithAttorney Referrals
Menu  OUR ATTORNEYSRobert H. DelleckerBrian T. WilsonSamuel P. KingKenneth J. McKennaWilliam E. RuffierAnthony F. SosWilliam J. Tonelli IIIDaniel E. Smith IIRyan YoungABOUT THE FIRMWho We helpWhy UsOur ApproachPRACTICE AREASBuilding DefectsBurn & FireBusiness TortsCar accidentsConstruction DefectsConstruction NegligenceDiabetic KetoacidosisDog Bite InjuriesElder Financial AbuseERCP MalpracticeHurricane Property DamageInsurance Bad FaithMedical MalpracticeMisdiagnosed AbdominalMotorcycle AccidentsNursing Home AbuseNursing Home NegligencePediatric Hip DysplasiaPediatric RetinoblastomaPremises LiabilityProduct LiabilityRollover Car AccidentsTourist InjuriesTruck AccidentsUnnecessary HysterectomyUnnecessary SurgeryWater InjuriesWrongful DeathCONTACT US
Select Page
Privacy PolicyPrivacy Policy for Dellecker, Wilson, King, McKenna, Ruffier, & Sos LLP.www.dwklaw.comAt Dellecker, Wilson, King, McKenna, Ruffier, & Sos LLP we recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use www.dwklaw.com, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.Dellecker, Wilson, King, McKenna, Ruffier, & Sos LLP strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our online visitors’ privacy on our website.Personal Information www.dwklaw.com collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to our website only on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email address, company name and telephone number.This information is collected if you request information from us, sign up to join our email list or request some other service or information from us. The information collected is internally reviewed, used to improve the content of our website, notify our visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries.Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in our files. If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information, we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. Personal information received from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and will not be sold or provided to third parties.Use of Cookies and Web BeaconsWe may use cookies to help you personalize your online experience. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize the sites pages, or register with any of our site’s services, a cookie enables www.dwklaw.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits.A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your journey around a single website or collection of sites. They are also referred to as web bugs and are commonly used by sites that hire third-party services to monitor traffic. They may be used in association with cookies to understand how visitors interact with the pages and content on the pages of a web site.Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions shouldn’t cause a problem with our site, should you so choose.Children’s Online Privacy Protection ActThis website is directed to adults; it is not directed to children under the age of 13. We operate our site in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.Non-Personal InformationIn some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. The information collected is used solely for internal review and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.Release of InformationIf www.dwklaw.com is ever sold, the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make of us.How You Can Correct or Remove InformationWe provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information through our website and would like that information deleted from our records or would like to update or correct that information, please use our Contact Us page.Updates and Effective Datewww.dwklaw.com reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.Agreeing to TermsIf you do not agree to www.dwklaw.com Privacy Policy as posted here for this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site.Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy. Have Legal Questions?
The use of the Internet or this form for communication with the firm or any individual member of the firm does not establish an attorney-client relationship. Confidential or time-sensitive information should not be sent through this form. We do not undertake representation of your claims until all parties involved have entered into a signed agreement. If we have not entered into a signed agreement with you, you may want to speak with other attorneys regarding your claims since statutes of limitations may apply.(407) 244-3000Contact Info719 Vassar Street Orlando, FL, 32804Toll Free:888-726-6735Local:407-244-3000Facsimile:407-244-3033Office Hours:Mon-Thu8:30 AM to 5:00 PMFriday8:30 AM to 4:00 PM“Shortly after being injured in the line-of-duty in 2002, I believe I was one of Dan Smith’s first comp cases that he was assigned. When my wife and I met with him, we never doubted his ability or drive. Dan was always professional, straight forward and took great care of us for the more than 14 years he represented me. He is a great attorney, but more importantly he is a great person and now friend. If you need an attorney, we highly recommend Dan to represent you and to be in your corner.” Jhon B.“Son injured at Disney World.
8 year old case resurrected at the 5th Court of Appeal.
Dellecker Wilson saw the validity of and value in the case and through another two and one half years realized a significant judgement for the injury sustained.
This firm is nothing but highly professional, dedicated, diligent, compassionate and beyond reproach. Kudos to our team led by Ken McKenna.
Doubtful there could be a smarter bunch of attorneys anywhere.” Dave P.“I was injured after being hit by a car while riding my bike and a good friend referred me to Tony Sos. I did not know where to begin the legal process, but Tony and his staff helped me navigate the road to recovery and settlement with honesty and integrity. Tony and his Paralegal, Joy, were always there when I had questions and kept me informed every step of the way. They helped me focus on my healing and recovery while they handled the legal issues of my case. I highly recommend Tony Sos and his staff!” Mary C.Contact InformationDELLECKER, WILSON, KING, MCKENNA, RUFFIER & SOS, LLP719 Vassar Street Orlando, FL, 32804Toll Free: 888-726-6735 Local: 407-244-3000 Facsimile: 407-244-3033 Office Hours: 8:30 AM to 5:00 PM Contact UsMap
Facebook
Twitter Copyright © 2020 | Dellecker, Wilson, King, McKenna, Ruffier, & Sos | Privacy Policy | Sitemap |
